export const generalQuestions = {
  questionsTitle: "General Questions",
  item: [
    {
      question: "Do you have Spanish speaking services?",
      answer:
        "Yes! We have bilingual services for Loans, Teller, Member Services, and Management at our branches. You can switch our website to Spanish. Si! Contamos con servicios bilingües para Préstamos, Cajeros, Representante de Servicios Financieros y Gerente de Administración en nuestras sucursales. Puede cambiar el sitio web a español.",
    },
    {
      question: "What is your Routing Number?",
      answer: "311985791",
    },
    {
      question: "What is my balance?",
      answer:
        "Please log into Home Banking, the mobile app, or use audio response to get your current balance. Account balances cannot be answered after hours by a representative.",
    },
    {
      question: "Can I join online?",
      answer:
        "Please log into Home Banking, the mobile app, or use audio response to get your current balance. Account balances cannot be answered after hours by a representative.",
    },
    {
      question: "How can I join the credit union?",
      answer:
        "You can join Telco Plus Credit Union if you live or work in Gregg or Smith County, work for one of our 150+ sponsor companies, or through family.  If you’re not sure if your company is on the list, please send us an email and we will check for you.  You will also need one form of ID and $5 deposit for your membership.",
    },
    {
      question: "What is my login?",
      answer:
        "Your initial Username for Home Banking and mobile app is your Telco Plus member number. We urge you to immediately change this to something else when you log in for the first time.  You can change your password in Home Banking.  Click on the User Icon on the top right of your screen that will take you to Profile & Settings, then select Change Username.",
    },
    {
      question: "How do I unlock my account?",
      answer:
        "You can either click on Forgot Password to reset your password or call during lobby hours to be unlocked. Longview 903-753-5588 or Tyler 903-597-4321",
    },
    {
      question: "How do I update my address?",
      answer:
        "You can send a Secure Message through the app or Home Banking, or by calling member services during lobby hours.  Be sure to let us know if you are on multiple accounts and if your email or phone number changed.  Failure to update your address could result in a $2 returned mail fee.",
    },
    {
      question: "How to use the mobile app?",
      answer: `Please download the Telco Plus Credit Union mobile app to your device. It is the same login information as Home Banking. If you have never used either service, you will need to use the "enroll now" option.`,
    },
    {
      question: "I lost my debit card, what should I do?",
      answer: `Use your Mobile app or Home Banking to turn your debit card to “Freeze”.  When you find your card, you can “Unfreeze” it the same way.  If you can't find it or think it was stolen, please call us during lobby hours.  If after hours, please call 903-534-2888 to report it stolen.`,
    },
    {
      question: "Is my money safe at a credit union?",
      answer: `Of course!  Credit unions use the NCUA which is very similar to the FDIC that is used by banks. For more information about the NCUA please follow the link. https://www.ncua.gov/`,
    },
    {
      question: "I can't remember my PIN for my debit card?",
      answer: `For security reasons we cannot reset PINs for members over the phone or through online services.  You can reset your pin in the lobby or by calling the automated system 866-762-0558. For this to work, all of your information must be correct in our system.`,
    },
    {
      question: "My card is not working?",
      answer: `First check your balance. If you have available funds, try running the card again.  If your card still doesn't work, either the chip has broken in the card, or your card has been shut down due to suspicious activity.  You will need to call the 866 number back to verify your most recent transaction to lift the hot card status. https://www.telcoplus.org/pages/contact-us.php.`,
    },
    {
      question: "How can I order a new card?",
      answer: `You can come by any branch to pick up an instant issue debit card. You can also order a new card by secure email through the app or Home Banking or by calling member services during lobby hours. The card will be mailed to you in 7 to 10 days, to the address on file. Please see the Fee Schedule for card replacement cost.`,
    },
    {
      question: "What are your hours?",
      answer: `The lobby is 9 a.m. to 5:30 p.m. Monday through Wednesday; 9 a.m. to 6 p.m. on Thursday and Friday; and 9 a.m. to Noon on Saturdays.

      Longview Drive Thru is 7:30 a.m. to 5:30 p.m. Monday through Wednesday and 7:30 a.m. to 6 p.m. Thursday and Friday; and 9 a.m. to Noon on Saturdays.
      
      The Tyler branch drive-thru opens at 8:30 a.m Monday – Friday and 9 a.m. on Saturdays.`,
    },
    {
      question: "Do you do shared branching through the drive-thru?",
      answer: `No, we do not. For a full list of shared branching services please visit this section of the website. https://www.telcoplus.org/pages/atm-services.php`,
    },
    {
      question: "When will I get my deposit?",
      answer: `Deposits are processed several times throughout the day. Most payroll deposits are in the accounts 48 hours early if the file is sent early.  Sometimes you can see pending deposits, that means orders were sent but not the funds.`,
    },
    {
      question: "Do you have instant issue cards?",
      answer: `Yes! Debit cards can be printed onsite, and we have several styles to select from.  Come see us if you need new a card.`,
    },
    {
      question: "Do you have gift cards?",
      answer: `Yes, we have several different styles of gift cards that can be purchased. You can load up to $1,000 on a gift card. You can send a request for a gift card through secure email in Home Banking, App, or make a purchase in person.  Give the gift of choice today!`,
    },
  ],
};

export const loanQuestions = {
  questionsTitle: "Loans Questions",
  item: [
    {
      question: "What type of loans do you offer?",
      answer: `We offer loans little as $300 all the way to mortgages.  Please visit the loan page for all the loans and products that we offer. https://www.telcoplus.org/pages/loans-index.php. If you are not a member, you can apply for a loan before you join!  Non-members can apply for loans on the website and Members can apply in Home Banking. https://www.telcoplus.org/pages/loan-application.php`,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who do I need to speak to if I am having a problem paying my loan?",
      answer: `You can call your loan officer to discuss the problem or the Collection department at the Longview branch to discuss your options. 903-753-5588. WE DO HAVE OPTIONS!`,
    },
    {
      question: "Do I need to make an appointment to see a lender?",
      answer: `Appointments are preferred at the Longview branch due to high demand and not to waste your time.  The Tyler branch accepts walk-ins and appointments.  You can call or email a lender to see if there is a good time to come in. loanlist@telcoplus.org or 903-753-5588, 903-597-4321`,
    },
    {
      question: "How to make a loan payment?",
      answer: `You can set up auto draft through payroll to receive a discount on your loan rate.  If you prefer to make your payments on your own, you have several options:  Mail in your payment and voucher, pay in person with a check, cash, depositing payment in the drop box, or credit card, or transfer money using Home Banking or App for free.  You can pay online in Home Banking or the App using a debit card from another financial institution. Please see the Fee Schedule for the cost.`,
    },
    {
      question: "Can I lower my loan rate with Telco Plus?",
      answer: `Secured Consumer Loans except mortgage loans or credit cards, are eligible to be re-evaluated after 12 months to see if you qualify for a lower interest rate. Credit scores dramatically improve after 12 months of good payment history, and this could put you in a lower interest rate category.
      You must ask for the re-evaluation. Only one request per 12 months, only one rate change per loan. Min 12-months of consecutive on time payments.   IF you think you qualify for a review you can email loan review requests to:  loanlist@telcoplus.org`,
    },
    {
      question:
        "How long do I have to wait to refinance my auto after buying it?",
      answer: `You can refinance your car the very next day! Regardless of what the salesperson might have told you, you do not have to wait to refinance for a better deal with us.`,
    },
    {
      question: "What documents are needed to do an auto refinance?",
      answer: `The purchase documents. Typically, we ask people to bring the “fat” envelope the dealer gave them when they purchased the vehicle. This way we can get what we need to photocopy. The purchase contract shows interest rate, term, and if applicable the gap and extended warranty information and who the vehicle was financed with.`,
    },
    {
      question: "Do you have credit cards?",
      answer: `Yes, we have VISA® credit cards. Credit qualifications apply and you can apply on the website or in Home Banking.

      We also have secured credit cards with no credit check. A deposit is required and with a good payment history the card can be converted to a regular credit card. Both card types report to all 3 bureaus to help build better a credit score.`,
    },
    {
      question: "How to make a VISA® credit card payment?",
      answer: `You can transfer money from your Telco Plus account to make a payment or use the Visa card payment website to make a payment. www.ezcardinfo.com. You can mail the payment to VISA PO Box 4521, Carol Stream, IL 60197-4521. *Payments will be reflected the next day.`,
    },
    {
      question:
        "How to view VISA® credit card transactions, balances, and print statements?",
      answer: `You can use the www.ezccardinfo.com to manage your credit card. If you need additional help, please see Member Services.`,
    },
    {
      question:
        "How to view VISA® credit card transactions, balances, and print statements?",
      answer: `You can use the www.ezccardinfo.com to manage your credit card. If you need additional help, please see Member Services.`,
    },
  ],
};
